Viewers all over the world,
wherever you are, whatever you are doing at this moment -
right now receive your healing, in the name of Jesus!
Receive your healing, in the name of Jesus!
Receive your deliverance, in the name of Jesus!
There’s a wonderful name Jesus
There is no other name I know
Receive your deliverance, in the name of Jesus!
Right now receive your healing, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus’ Name
What manner of man is Jesus?
When He says, “Yes” no one can say, “No”.
Receive your healing, in the name of Jesus!
Receive your deliverance, in the name of Jesus!
Freedom!
Cover yourself with the Blood of Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus!
In Jesus Christ’s name!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus’ Name
Hallelujah!
Rejoice, in the name of Jesus; give thanks to Him.
Give thanks to Him.
TT Robert Begier 30/04/2019